That's the start solving link, at least exercises and master the link, at least.
We have an exercise number 39 to reverse the linkage list, so we have the linked list of we need to
start reversing it to read and the output by 100, 200 300, we will reverse it by making 300 to 100
in one country.
So we make the end as a the start and move the hat to the last note and make the first note as pointing
to that now which detect and of an injured list.
So this is the reversing of link, at least.
So in order to reverse the linked list in sea, we need to create a void method called reverse list.
We pass inside the truck, no head pointer.
And we create strict no current equal to that.
And the previous equal to no.
And we create in next struck no point.
We start by making the while loop wise current does not equal to null, then next equal current next.
This is the point we are copying the point, OK?
And the current point that next.
Equal to previous, we are just switching the current with the previous and previous with the next previous
equal to current and current equal to next.
This is how we can reverse the linked list.
And then last step by making the had equal to proof which previous.
OK, this is the algorithm behind the reversing of the link, at least in C.
Let's see.
And Java a programming language.
How we can make a reversing of the link, at least first of all, will create a class called ENCODE
List.
We have seen it and before and we have is that the class note?
This is the structure of the note as in C.
And the function to reverse the link, at least, is called reverse it, return, not okay.
We create three nodes Prev.
Previous Current and next.
They are referring to NULL.
But the current equal to not that we have been best, while current does not equal to none.
We are not reaching the end.
Make next equal care.
And that next turn that next equals to prove and prove equal to current and current quota next.
That same algorithm ANC, but different syntax and some basics like structure and structure and class
not equal to Prev.
And here we need to return.
Not because the function to reverse the link at least kind of has a returning type of type not OK.
So this is how we reverse the linkage lest we create that method reverse list and we start reversing
it by specifying the current next and.